http://www.handmadebats.co.uk/privacy-policy

Warsop StebbingWarsop StebbingWarsop StebbingWarsop StebbingWarsop StebbingWarsop StebbingWarsop StebbingWarsop StebbingHomeStoreClothingAbout usCovid-19 instore measuresContact usOur HeritageFAQBat RepairsMoreHomeStoreClothingAbout usCovid-19 instore measuresContact usOur HeritageFAQBat RepairsHomeStoreClothingAbout us
Privacy PolicyAs a small family run business our key priority is our customers and we take your privacy seriously, we will only use your details to fulfill orders and keep you up to date with our products.This notice explains what personal data (information) we hold about you, how we collect it, and how we use and may share information about you during our trading relationship and after it ends. We are required to notify you of this information under data protection legislation. Please ensure that you read this notice.Data Protection principlesWarsop-Stebbing is a ‘data controller’ and gathers and uses certain information about you.We will comply with the data protection principles when gathering and using personal information, as set out in our data protection policy.About the information we collect & holdThe table set out in the Customer Privacy Schedule (which can be downloaded below) summarises the information we collect and hold, how and why we do so, how we use it and with whom it may be shared.We may also need to share some of the categories of personal information set out in the Schedule with other parties, such as external contractors and our professional advisers. The recipient of the information will be bound by confidentiality obligations. We may also be required to share some personal information as required to comply with thelaw.We seek to ensure that our information collection and processing is always proportionate. We will notify you of any changes to information we collect or to the purposes for which we collect and process it.Where information may beheldInformation may be held at our offices, on our online store, service providers such as courier companies.How long we keep your informationWe keep your information during and after our trading relationship for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal information is processed. Your rights to correct and access your information and to ask for it to be erased.Please contact our workshop on 01245 400 434, if (in accordance with applicable law) you would like to correct or request access to information that we hold relating to you or if you have any questions about this notice. You also have the right to ask for some but not all of the information we hold and process to be erased (the ‘right to be forgotten’) in certain circumstances. The owners of Warsop-Stebbing will provide you with further information about the right to be forgotten, if you ask forit.Keeping your personal information secureWe have appropriate security measures in place to prevent personal information from being accidentally lost, or used or accessed in an unauthorised way. We limit access to your personal information to those who have a genuine business need to know it. Those processing your information will do so only in an authorised manner and are subject to a duty of confidentiality.We also have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach. We will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected data security breach where we are legally required to do so.How to complainWe hope that we can can resolve any query or concern you raise about our use of your information. If not, contact the Information Commissioner at ico.org.uk/concerns/ or telephone:03031231113 for further information about your rights and how to make a formal complaint.
Customer Privacy ScheduleHow we collect and use your data in an easy to understand table.Customer Privacy Schedule (pdf)Download
Copyright © 2020 Warsop Cricket - All Rights Reserved.Contact usSize GuideDeliveryBat Care GuideWarsop Sunday LeaguePrivacy PolicyTerms and Conditions
